(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
【お弁当】差し入れ参加者様
[Lunch Box] Support Participants
フルシーンの
A full scene
ただ触れて抱きしめていたいよ
I just want to touch you and hold you tight
たとえ暗い夜の底で
Even at the bottom of a dark night
少し弾んで
Bounce a little
なんてね
Just kidding
開演までしばらくお待ちください。
Please wait a moment until the performance begins.
SNSでの感想投稿OK
Posting impressions on SNS is OK
【フラスタ】差し入れ参加者様
[Flower Stand] Support Participants
超電磁波に
In the super electromagnetic waves
紛れて まるごと書き写そう
Get mixed in and copy it all down
空の彼方へ...
To the beyond of the sky...
大盤振るわせてる胸 踊るスパギンガの目
My heart is pounding, eyes dancing in the super galaxy
アドベンチャラリラリラ 8分先の未来 誰が求めてる
Adventure-la-li-la-li-la, who is looking for a future 8 minutes away?
無限大の可能性持て
Have infinite possibilities
超電磁波にジャンプして まるごと書き写そう
Jump into the super electromagnetic waves and copy it all down
空の彼方へ 踊れ踊れ
To the beyond of the sky, dance, dance
証明する 超科学的サンデーパ
Proving it, super-scientific Sunday Party
飛び込む バイノーラル
Dive in, binaural
午前零時の帳 街を
At the stroke of midnight, the town...
独り占めしてる気分
I feel like I have it all to myself
散らばったビル灯り 失ったものばかり瞬いている
Scattered building lights, only the things I lost are twinkling
目を閉じて躍ろう
Close your eyes and dance
さよならって 終われないし
I can't just end with a goodbye
永遠の夜なんてないのはわかってる
I know there's no such thing as an eternal night
【お弁当】差し入れ参加者様
[Bento Lunch] Refreshment Gift Participants
君と明かす夜会
A night party spent with you
明日もまた同じ
Tomorrow too, if the same
朝日が昇るなら
morning sun rises
青く光る夜会
A blue shining night party
星空のミラーボール
A starry sky mirror ball
私を照らして
Illuminate me
開演までしばらくお待ちください。
The show will begin shortly. Please wait.
タップで地球揺らすくらい
Enough to shake the earth with a tap
ここで踊り明かそう
Let's dance the night away here
【フラスタ】差し入れ参加者様
[Flower Stand] Refreshment Gift Participants
午前5時の夜明けの街で
In the city at dawn at 5 AM
なんか独りぼっちな気分
Feeling somewhat lonely
ぼんやり眺めるベッド 期待してる
Gazing blankly at the bed, I'm expecting
君の足音を
the sound of your footsteps
触れた手も
Even touched hands
触れられないし
can't be touched
運命の赤い糸なんて 知らないし
And I don't know about the red thread of fate
それでも君と繋がっていたい
Even so, I want to stay connected with you
明るくなる空に この想い乗せて
Placing these feelings on the brightening sky
何も見えない
Nothing can be seen
灰色に流れる
Streaming through the grey
雲間から差し込む
shining through the clouds
たっぷり深呼吸して
Taking a deep breath
境界線を越える
I'll cross the boundary
なんであなたにはできないの？なんてさ
"Why can't you do it?" they say
陰口言われたり 呆れられたり 口角下がる エブリデイ
People talk behind my back, get fed up; corners of my mouth drop every day
電車は私を置き去りにしちゃうし
The train leaves me behind
刃物野菜もスピード早すぎだね
Knives and vegetables, the speed is just too fast
ありのままの素敵さだけじゃ足りないんだ Take me
Just being wonderful as you are isn't enough, Take me
毎日死ぬほど頑張ってやっとここまで連れてきたんだ
I've worked hard enough to die every day to finally bring it this far
あなたには分からない
You don't understand
分かってほしくない
I don't want you to understand
私の苦労も 雲もどきか ご存知ないでいてね
My hardships, not even knowing if they are cloud-like, please keep not knowing
きっとあなたにもできるはず なんてさ
"Surely you can do it too," they say
言うほど無責任にはなりたくない
I don't want to be as irresponsible as saying that
それでも死ぬほど頑張って駆ける値打ちはあると思った
Even so, I thought it was worth running and working hard enough to die
投げ出したくなるよ でも諦めたくはない
I want to throw it all away, but I don't want to give up
私の未来も
My future
失敗も全部 私だけのもの
My failures too, they are all mine alone
差し入れを贈ってくださった皆様、本当にありがとうございます！
To everyone who sent refreshments, thank you very much!
終わらない　私の未来も
My future is never-ending, too.
失敗も全部　私色だよ
Even my failures are all my color.
気づかない　気づかないでいて　可愛いだけの私でいい
Don't notice, please don't notice, I'm fine being just a "cute girl".
開演までしばらくお待ちください。
Please wait a while until the show starts.
スクリーンショットをSNSにアップロード投稿OK / SNSでの感想投稿OK
Upload and post screenshots to SNS OK / OK to post your impressions on SNS
録画、録音、ミラー配信や違法アップロードは固く禁止します。
Recording, recording, mirror distribution, and illegal uploading are strictly prohibited.
胸に詰め込んだ　夢はくしゃくしゃで
The dreams I've packed in my chest are all crumpled up,
勇気がいるけど　君にだけは見せようかななんてね
And I need courage, but maybe I'll show them only to you. Just kidding!
一緒にゆけるかな　秘密の場所を
I wonder if we can go together, to that secret place...
渡してゆこう
Let's pass it on.
深呼吸　そしてパッと言葉
A deep breath, and then the words pop out.
空、誰にももらっちゃうくらい
Sora, so much that anyone would take them.
最高のヒロインを　上手くいかない今日だって
The best heroine, even on days when things don't go well,
教科書見ずに閉じちゃったら　なんてやりそうだ
I might just close the textbook without looking—that's so like me.
落書きのなかに隠してた思いを
The feelings I kept hidden within my doodles,
君とこうして分かち合えたなんて
Being able to share them with you like this...
嘘みたいだなぁ
...it feels like a dream.
もっと　またたいて印して
Twinkle even more, and leave your mark.
一歩ずつかな　成長できるかな
One step at a time, I wonder if I can grow?
共に明日を　駆け抜けよう
Let's run through tomorrow together.
ドンドン増えた　宝物の中
Amidst the treasures that keep on growing,
リボン添えて　繋いでゆこう
Let's add a ribbon and tie them together.
立ち止まらないよ　楽しかった日々ほら
I won't stop, look at those happy days!
昨日よりも加速してる
They're accelerating even more than yesterday.
ちゃんと繋いでて
Make sure to hold on tight.
簡単じゃないホームの　かけ声は
The cheers at our home base, which isn't easy,
いつも君が明るく放って　支えてくれる
You always call them out brightly and support me.
ずっと　刻まれて光るよ
They'll be etched in my heart and shine forever.
三つ数えたら　砂に書いた絵
If you count to three, the drawing in the sand...
消えてしまうけど　それと同じで
...will disappear, and just like that...
君の顔ばかり　浮かべてたら
...if I keep imagining your face...
アイスみたいに　とろけては
...I'll start to melt just like ice cream.
差し入れを贈ってくださった皆様、本当にありがとうございました！
To everyone who sent a gift, thank you very much!
...んなくなる
...will disappear
夢も愛も ギュッとして いっぱいだから
I've packed my dreams and love so tight,
持ちきれない
That I can't hold them all anymore.
でも欲張りすぎて きっと 落ちていく
But I'm being too greedy, so I'm sure I'll fall down.
もうラカラカチュチュ 恋に落ちちゃって
Now, laka-laka chu-chu, I've fallen in love,
ギュッギュッもう戻れない
Tightly, tightly, I can't go back now.
あれあれなんで ふわっと心が まだ熱くなるの
Oh, oh, why is my heart still feeling so light and warm?
ラカラカチュチュ 君の重力で
Laka-laka chu-chu, with your gravity,
ギュッギュッ引き寄せて
Tightly, tightly, pulling me in.
カレイドスコープ 覗いてるみたいで ねえキラキラな
It's like looking through a kaleidoscope, hey, it's so sparkly.
未来 見たい 分からない
I want to see the future, but I don't know it yet.
Ah Up and Down で 振り回す
Ah, tossing and turning with up and down,
Yo & Day 今日は 四六時中
Yo & Day, today, all day long,
カレンダー 30日でも 足りない
Even 30 days on a calendar aren't enough.
あれもこれもそれも 全部したい
I want to do this, that, and everything!
キュンキュンキュン上昇 ドキドキ白昼夢
Kyun kyun kyun rising, a heart-pounding daydream,
キュンキュンキュン降下 深呼吸
Kyun kyun kyun falling, take a deep breath.
キュンキュンキュン上昇 ラブリーメンタル
Kyun kyun kyun rising, lovely mental state,
キュンキュンキュン降下 手を繋ごう
Kyun kyun kyun falling, let's hold hands.
無限大の愛だけど
It's an infinite love,
失敗だけど 諦めない
Even if I fail, I won't give up.
まだ欲張りだから 君と
Because I'm still greedy, with you,
落ちていく
I'm falling down.
もうラカラカチュチュ 心がはまって
Now, laka-laka chu-chu, my heart is stuck,
ギュッギュッ抜け出せない
Tightly, tightly, I can't escape.
あれあれなんで 目まぐるしい心が まだ熱くなるの
Oh, oh, why is my dizzy heart still feeling so warm?
ラカラカチュチュ スピード重視で
Laka-laka chu-chu, prioritizing speed,
ギュッギュッ引き寄せて
Tightly, tightly, pulling me in.
カレイドスコープ 覗いてるみたいで ねえキラキラな
It's like looking through a kaleidoscope, hey, it's so sparkly.
未来 見たい 分からない
I want to see the future, but I don't know it yet.
ちっぽけだな 理想とか
Ideals are such small things,
私はまだ 未完成で
I am still incomplete.
あの空に 目を細めてしまうんだ
I find myself squinting at that sky.
考えても どうしようもないことだと
Even if I think about it, it's something I can't help.
止めな 心から 色々込み上げてくるけど
Stop it, all sorts of things are welling up from my heart, but...
だからこそ 笑顔でね
That's why, with a smile,
だからこそ 負けないで
That's why, don't give up.
羽ばたくための 羽を手にして 飛び立っていくんだよ
Take hold of the wings to fly and take flight.
空を飛んでいこう 飛んでいこう 色づいていく夢 ほら虹空
Let's fly through the sky, fly, dreams gaining color, look, a rainbow sky.
青を待ってみよう 待ってみよう 少し大きくなったね
Let's wait for the blue, wait, you've grown a little bigger, haven't you?
空は青い色 青い色 少し経ったら すぐに茜色
The sky is blue, blue, and after a little while, it's immediately madder red.
ちょっと迷っても 迷っても ゆっくり風を受けて
Even if you're a little lost, lost, just slowly catch the wind.
空に願いを
A wish to the sky,
何遍も言うよ 口ずさんで
I'll say it over and over, humming along.
いつしか 忘れていた 奇跡の 閉じ方を探そう
Let's find the way to close the miracles we'd forgotten at some point.
ある時は 笑顔でね
Sometimes with a smile,
ある時は 泣き顔で
Sometimes with a crying face.
見上げたあの空 目印にして 羽ばたいていくんだよ
Using that sky we looked up at as a landmark, we'll take flight.
差し入れを贈ってくださった皆様、本当にありがとうございます！
Thank you very much to everyone who sent donations!
空を飛んで行こう　飛んで行こう
Let's fly through the sky, let's fly
色付き始めた夢は止まらない
The dreams that have begun to take color won't stop
開演までしばらくお待ちください。
Please wait a while until the performance starts.
もっと伝えよう　伝えよう
Let's convey more, let's convey
ラララ　こんなメロディで
La la la, with a melody like this
空は青い色　青い色
The sky is blue, a blue color
そっと覗いたら　すぐに茜色
If I take a peek, it soon turns madder red
ちょっと寂しくて　眩しくて
A little lonely, a little dazzling
だけど温かい気持ち
But it's a warm feeling
手を取り合って　笑い合ってくれるかな
Will you hold my hand and laugh with me?
これからも私のこと　よろしくね
Please continue to support me from now on
今日の日を麗らかに歌いながら
While singing brightly about today
空を飛んで行こう　飛んで行こう
Let's fly through the sky, let's fly
差し入れを贈ってくださった皆様、本当にありがとうございます！
Thank you very much to everyone who sent donations!
バーチャル リアル どっちがいい？
Virtual or real, which is better?
バーチャル リアル どっちもいい！
Virtual, real, both are good!
サムネタップ　はじめまして
Tap the thumbnail, nice to meet you
キュンとしたならハート押して
If your heart skips a beat, press the heart
通知はオン　いつでもカモン
Notifications on, come anytime
一緒に踊ろう　オン・アンド・オン
Let's dance together, on and on
甘いお菓子食べたいけどダイエット中
I want to eat sweet treats but I'm on a diet
君の好みにアップデート中
Updating to your liking
ポチり更新　君と更新
Clicking and updating, updating with you
もっと推してほしいのな
I want you to support me more
バーチャル　リアル　どっちが好き？
Virtual, real, which do you like?
繋がる　1・2・3　次元
Connecting, 1, 2, 3 dimensions
ワン・ツー・スリーで飛び越えて
Jump over on one, two, three
今やメタもリアルです
Now meta is also real
チグハグしないで　ラブとピースで
Don't be mismatched, with love and peace
トキメイカ　トキカケガ
Tokimeika, Tokikakega
紡ぎ出す　Dreaming world
Weaving a dreaming world
待てれば最強　バーチャリアル
If you can wait, it's the strongest Virtua-Real
2回スワイプ　ビート足して
Swipe twice, add some beat
キュンとしたなら手叩いて
If your heart skips a beat, clap your hands
自撮りも　エンジョイも
Selfies and enjoying too
一緒に踊ろう　オン・アンド・オン
Let's dance together, on and on
お祝い事ならコラボ中
If it's a celebration, we're collaborating
新しいことリサーチ中
Researching new things
ピピピテレパシー　今日も配信
Pi-pi-pi telepathy, streaming today too
もっとハジケたいのな
I want to burst out more
ねえねえ　どっち可愛い？
Hey hey, which is cute?
どっちも可愛い！
Both are cute!
お菓子食べたいけどダイエット中
I want to eat sweet treats but I'm on a diet
君の好みにアップデート中
Updating to your liking
ポチり更新　君と更新
Clicking and updating, updating with you
もっと推してほしいのな
I want you to support me more
バーチャル　リアル　どっちが好き？
Virtual, real, which do you like?
バーチャル　リアル　どっちも好き
Virtual, real, I like both
繋がる　1・2・3　次元
Connecting, 1, 2, 3 dimensions
ワン・ツー・スリーで飛び越えて
Jump over on one, two, three
今やメタもリアルです
Now meta is also real
チグハグしないで　ラブとピースで
Don't be mismatched, with love and peace
トキメイカ　トキカケガ
Tokimeika, Tokikakega
紡ぎ出す　Dreaming world
Weaving a dreaming world
待てれば最強　バーチャリアル
If you can wait, it's the strongest Virtua-Real
バーチャル リアル どっちがいい？
Virtual or real, which is better?
バーチャル リアル どっちもいい！
Virtual, real, both are good!
開演までしばらくお待ちください。
Please wait a while until the performance starts.
しばらくお待ちください。
Please wait a moment.
Please wait for a while.
しばらくお待ちください。
Please wait.
2025.10.1 Wed
8th Anniversary Party Starry Bl∞min'
with DJ Ankin
2019 1st year
2020 2nd year
2021 3rd year
2022 4th year
2023 5th year
2024 6th year
ARE YOU READY?
Starry Bl∞min'
8th Starry Bl∞min' Anniversary Party
降り注ぐ青い星に
Showering blue stars
恥じらいも強くなって
My bashfulness has grown stronger too
本当は震えている
I'm actually trembling
手足が隠せないよ
I can't hide my hands and feet
物語の先はもっと
The future of the story
きらびやかな色で描く
I'll paint with more brilliant colors
臆病な足音も
Even my cowardly footsteps
止められなかった昨日のことも
And the things from yesterday I couldn't stop
翼みたいに羽ばたいて
Flapping like wings
飛べたならいいのに
I wish I could fly
もう何もいらないから
Because I don't need anything else anymore
忘れさせないから
Because I won't let you forget
どこまでも遠くまでと
To wherever, as far as I can go
このまま振り向かないで
I won't look back just like this
輝く砂の波を
Over the waves of shining sand
あの闇を越えて
Beyond that darkness
満ちた翼で
With full-grown wings
もっと遠くへ
Further away
駆け出す空へ
Towards the sky I run into
みんなー！
Everyone!
隠した指は見つかった
I found the hidden finger
それと不意のヒビが入っちゃった
And a crack suddenly appeared
いつしか傷つけた
Before I knew it, I had hurt
君のスペシャルな夢の隅
A corner of your special dream
鼓動みたいに熱く
Hot like a heartbeat
願えたらいいのに
I wish I could pray
気がついた 檻の中で
I realized within the cage
夢の隅で光って
Shining in a corner of a dream
同じ顔は
The same faces
きっと大事なものだから
Because they're surely precious
間違えても 躓いても
Even if I make mistakes, even if I stumble
離さないでいよう
Let's not let go
空の果てまで
To the ends of the sky
この先を見つめて
Gazing at what lies ahead
飛びたいの
I want to fly
この命懸けて
With my life on the line
もう何もいらないから
Because I don't need anything else anymore
忘れさせないから
Because I won't let you forget
どこまでも続く
Continuing endlessly
ありのままずっと
Forever as I am
輝けるように
So that I can shine
碧い闇を越えて
Beyond the blue darkness
いつだって笑っていてよ
Always be smiling
ずっと
Forever
行こう 有限の宇宙（そら）へ
Let's go to the finite sky
このまま終われないんだ
It can't end like this
答えを延々と探して駆け抜けて
Searching for answers endlessly, running through
何者かになりたくて
Wanting to become someone
燦々と降る夕立を
The brilliant evening shower falling
ただ眺めていた
I was just gazing at it
優しく寄り添って 心が晴れるのならば
If my heart clears up by gently snuggling up
翼が生えたようさ
It's like I've grown wings
今しがた
Just now
いつだって隣にいるから
Because I'll always be by your side
だって言葉紡いで歌うことが僕の運命だ
Because weaving words and singing is my destiny
世界にありふれた虚しささえも上書きして
Overwriting even the hollow feelings common in the world
路地裏に咲いた花のように宵を照らす
Lighting up the night like a flower blooming in a back alley
小さな光に憧れて
Longing for a small light
名前を持たない歌だって
Even a song without a name
神様は認めてくれない
God won't acknowledge it
一つ一つ枯れない花のように
Like flowers that don't wither, one by one
きのうの自分にさよならして
Saying goodbye to yesterday's self
こぼれた涙 蓋を笑えるその日まで
Until the day I can laugh at the tears that spilled
だって理想は遠ざかっていくばかり 脆かったんだよ
Because ideals are only getting further away, I was fragile
どれだけ手を伸ばして叫んだって届かないの
No matter how much I reach out and shout, I won't reach it
横目で見過ごしたあの日々さえ信じられるなら
If I can believe in even those days I looked away from
咆哮(ほうこう)振った歌響いて
The roaring song resonates
足跡の向こう側が今日も煩(うるさ)い
The other side of the footprints is noisy today too
行き止まりばかり足が竦(すく)んで立てないよ
My legs are trembling with only dead ends, I can't stand
音のない世界から君を見つけて連れ出すんだ
I'll find you from the silent world and take you away
言葉紡いで歌うことが僕の運命だ
Weaving words and singing is my destiny
世界にありふれた虚しささえも上書きして
Overwriting even the hollow feelings common in the world
路地裏に咲いた花のように宵を照らす
Lighting up the night like a flower blooming in a back alley
小さな光に憧れて
Longing for a small light
君の隣で笑えたなら
If I could laugh by your side
それなら！
If so!
瞳の奥まで
To the depths of your eyes
届くまで叫ぼう
Let's shout until it reaches
それなら彼方まで
If so, to the beyond
嗚呼！
Ah!
さあ まだ鳴らしてる胸踊るスパークがね
Come on, the heart-dancing spark is still ringing
アヴァンチュラ 踊り
Aventurary dance
80年先の未来 誰もが求める 運命(ウェンウェン)
The future 80 years ahead that everyone seeks, destiny
8次元まで
To the 8th dimension
飛び込んで　地球上　混ぜ混ぜして　何度でもハジけちゃえ
Dive in, on this Earth, mix it all up, and burst out as many times as you like!
Beyond　パパッパ
Beyond papappa
Beyond　時代はぐるり回る
Beyond, the times go round and round
Beyond　ハジメタ　時代想像して
Beyond, it's started, imagine the times
さあ　時代の波へ
Come on, to the wave of the times
さあ　色の波へ
Come on, to the wave of colors
さあ　無限大の可能性
Come on, to infinite possibilities
超えてけ
Go beyond!
それで Happy　全速力　混ぜ混ぜして　いつまでもダンス中
Then Happy, at full speed, mix it all up, dancing forever
そのまま　体中踊れ踊れ
Just like that, let your whole body dance, dance
それで Happy　めぐりくる　混ぜ混ぜして　お友達
Then Happy, coming around, mix it all up, my friend
いつもハジけるよ
Always bursting out
ラララララ　ラララララ
La la la la la...
輝くのさ　全部ハジけちゃえ
Gonna shine, let it all burst out
ラララララ　ラララララ
La la la la la...
輝き溢れ出す　ステップ踏んで　ダンス中
Sparkle overflows, stepping along, in the middle of a dance
ラララララ　ラララララ
La la la la la...
共鳴する　情熱をぶつけ合えば
If we clash our resonating passion
Beyond　ラリラリ
Beyond rarirari
飛び込む　テクニカルバイブ
Diving in, technical vibe
Beyond　ライハッパ
Beyond raihappa
それで Happy　もっとさらに打ち明けて　魅せるユニバース
Then Happy, open up even more, a universe to show
Beyond　パパッパ
Beyond papappa
一人じゃいけないところまで
To a place I can't reach alone
見て　見て　震えるぜ
Look, look, it's shivering
見ていてね！
Keep watching!
さあ　時代を超えて
Come on, across the ages
さあ　希望の声
Come on, the voice of hope
さあ　巡り続ける時を
Come on, the time that continues to go around
超えてけ
Go beyond!
それで Happy　エネルギーと君との目　一生
Then Happy, energy and our eyes meeting, for a lifetime
目に見えない夢ここに秘めて
Hidden here is a dream invisible to the eye
爆上がり　始まった
Bursting up, it's started
永遠の輝きへ
Towards eternal brilliance
それで Happy　全速力　混ぜ混ぜして　いつまでもダンス中
Then Happy, at full speed, mix it all up, dancing forever
そのまま　体中踊れ踊れ
Just like that, let your whole body dance, dance
それで Happy　めぐりくる　混ぜ混ぜして　お友達
Then Happy, coming around, mix it all up, my friend
いつもハジけるよ
Always bursting out
ラララララ　ラララララ
La la la la la...
輝くのさ　全部ハジけちゃえ
Gonna shine, let it all burst out
ラララララ　ラララララ
La la la la la...
輝き溢れ出す　ステップ踏んで　ダンス中
Sparkle overflows, stepping along, in the middle of a dance
ラララララ　ラララララ
La la la la la...
おーおおー
Ohh oh-ohh
ラララララ　ラララララ
La la la la la...
それで Happy　輝きへ　ダンス中
Then Happy, towards brilliance, in the middle of a dance
はい！みんな！こんそめー！
Hi! Everyone! Kon-some-!
みんなの声が大きすぎて、オケが聞こえないレベルの大歓声、ありがとう！
Everyone's voices were so loud, it was a roar of cheers to the point I couldn't hear the backing track. Thank you!
ちょっと、一回聞いておこうかな？にゃー！にゃー！
I think I'll listen for a moment. Meow! Meow!
ということで、一年半ぶりのソラパなんですけど...
So, this is the first SoraPa in a year and a half...
ちょっと恒例のやつ、あ、やってもいい？
Can I do that usual thing? Ah, is it okay?
みんなー！
Everyone!
って言うんで、「はーい」とか言ってください。いきますよ！
I'll say that, so please say "Hi" or something. Here we go!
男の子ー！
Boys!
ちょっと、恥ずかしいかもしれない、ちょっと手だけ振ってもいいよ。
It might be a bit embarrassing, so you can just wave your hand if you like.
女の子ー！
Girls!
声聞こえた、ありがとう！
I heard your voices, thank you!
海外の方ー！
People from overseas!
すごい！そして、えーっと...
Amazing! And, um...
「めちゃ遠くから来たよ」って人！絶対自分が一番遠い、みたいな人、いる？
People who said "I came from really far away!" Is there anyone who's definitely the farthest?
あ、でも海外の方かな？ありがとうございます。
Ah, but maybe it's the overseas fans? Thank you very much.
そして、そうだね、未成年席の方ー！
And, let's see, the underage section!
いえーい！ありがとうございます。では、みんなで行くよ！
Yay! Thank you very much. Now, let's do it with everyone!
みんなー！
Everyone!
こっち側ー！
This side!
最後に、全員ー！
Finally, everyone!
ありがとう！はい、これね、これがやりたかったんだ、ずっと。へへ。
Thank you! Yes, this, I've wanted to do this for a long time. Hehe.
ヘイ！ハイッ！
Hey! Alright!
と、いうわけでですね、なんと
So, as it turns out...
YouTube で見てる皆さん、
everyone watching on YouTube,
無料配信はここまでなんです！
the free broadcast ends here!
えー！？
Ehhh?!
今来たばっかり？私も今来たばっかり！
You just got here? I just got here too!
そうだよーねー。わかるわかる。
I know, right? I totally get it.
えー、わかってるよー、
Yeah, I know...
コメントのみんなも見えてるよー。
I can see everyone in the comments too.
イエーイって言ってるなー。イエーイ。
"Yay," they're saying. Yay!
ちょっとラグってるのかもしれない。
Maybe there's a bit of lag.
今来たばっかりって書いてね。よろしく。
Make sure to write "I just got here." Thanks!
続きは、え、見たい人、概要欄から
For the rest, if you want to watch, please check the description...
見てもらえる...
...and find it there.
どこにあるのかなこれ。
Where is it, exactly?
どっかに概要欄のタグがあると思うんで、
I think there's a description tag somewhere,
そこらへんからちょっと見てもらえれば、
so if you could check that out,
嬉しいです！
I'd be so happy!
次の曲いっちゃおうかな？
Shall we move on to the next song?
まだまだ盛り上がれる？
Can we get even more hyped?
みんながおうちに帰ってくるの、待ってたよー！
I've been waiting for everyone to come home!
というわけで、次の曲は
With that, the next song is...
新アルバムからこの曲で！
...this one from my new album!
冒頭無料配信はこちらで終了です。
The initial free broadcast ends here.
★ライブチケット購入はコチラ >> SPWN
★ Purchase live tickets here >> SPWN
冒頭無料配信はこちらで終了です。ライブチケット購入はコチラ>> SPWN
The free preview of the broadcast ends here. Click here to purchase live tickets >> SPWN